Extra! Extra! Extra!
It says that Momose Naotora died!
Sounds like the Hyakko Party's finally finished.
We'll be able to walk down the street at night without fear!
Looks like they took an entire train down with them.
What a way to go out.
Curse you I say, curse you!
What have you done, Mikhail?! Curses!
Do you have any idea how hard I worked to make that?
All I did was release him from his suffering.
Surely there were other ways you could have done it!
Lord Kershner, tell him!
I've received a message from Lord Yevgraf.
The Ark of Sirius is not in this city.
So coming here was a waste.
No, no, no!
My research was not a waste!
We must return to Lord Yevgraf's side with all due haste.
I-I-I'm not giving up!
I have enough data now!
We'll be able to mass-produce them!
Damn you! Damn you I say! I'm...
Such an unruly man.
His research was only an imitation,
good only for draining our labor and money.
There is a more important task for us to attend to.
Those persistent, irritating insects.
The Jaegers.
We're going to exterminate the lot of them right here in this city.
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
Does this batch of flowers look like it'll be to your satisfaction, Yuliy?
This is pretty beat up.
Wouldn't we be better off just buying a new car?
I've got a better idea. How much cash do you think we can squeeze out of them for repairs?
Keep me out of it.
Yo, you've got some grease on your face.
Seriously?
Dude, your face!
This is why I hate dealing with oily stuff!
Just go take a bath when we're done!
Come on, let's get Yuliy to help too.
Huh?
He seems like he'd be good at complicated stuff like this.
Let's not bother him right now.
They didn't really look similar, did they.
Who didn't?
Yuliy and his brother didn't.
Well, it wouldn't be good if he looked like a vampire.
So he had become a vampire.
Yes.
He told me that as long as I was a Jaeger, we'd be enemies.
He also spoke of the Ark.
I was still young when Dogville was attacked,
and my people never really told me anything about the Ark.
However, my brother surely knows.
That may be why the vampires are keeping him alive.
Just what is the Ark?
What is my brother planning on doing with it?
Yuliy.
Do you want to leave the Jaegers?
If you do, you'll no longer need to fight your brother.
Revenge is my reason to live!
I have nothing but this job!
Weren't you the one who taught me that?
I have no idea how I'd be supposed to live if I stopped.
True, I taught you how to get revenge.
But that doesn't mean that's "how you live."
His name is Mikhail, right?
He's your brother, your only living kin.
To live with him is another choice that lies before you.
But my brother's a vampire...
What if there were a way to change that?
If, as he claimed, it was possible with the Ark to either kill or let live, then there may be.
If we learn more about the Ark, that may shed light on the question of how you might live.
But first, we must ascertain what the vampires are doing now.
The vampires used Alma Company to create that humanoid weapon.
We don't know what any of that has to do with the Ark,
but the question is what they'll do now that it's destroyed.
First you leave without seeking permission,
and now you tell me that you were on this train?
I apologize for worrying you.
Worry me you did. Who knows what could have happened if our guests had not been there.
Someone from the railway just came to deliver this to us.
I had allowed you to train in swordsmanship in order to train your body and spirit,
Explosion on Express Train
Hyakko Party Thought
but I now forbid you from touching a sword again.
Aspiring to study both the book and the sword is a thing of the past.
You need only focus on your education as the next head of the household.
Father, there are many things that I cannot learn through education in this world.
What?
I cannot accept that!
I want to learn more about this world, to experience it!
That I am to take your place makes that only more im—
Enough!
For heaven's sake.
Do you want me to forbid you from leaving the house?
In any case, just restrain yourself from now on.
What would your mother say if she were still—
I will not!
I will not restrain myself!
Nor stop studying the sword!
W-Wait right there, Ryouko!
Ryouko!
The capital's been buzzing with talk of the Hyakko Party all morning.
I doubt the police will take long to finish rounding up the remnants.
I see.
It's a shame what happened to General Kakizaki.
Yes.
After he finished his report, he took full responsibility for the incident
and took his own life.
I'm told that it was a respectable end, fitting of a warrior.
However, the incident is not over yet.
There's still Alma Company.
Ever since the incident at their Japanese branch,
much of their management, including the vice-president—
who was visiting from abroad—is nowhere to be found.
The Army and General Staff HQ are both desperately looking for them.
We've been tasked with joining the search for Alma's management.
It seems that if they're hiding here in the capital,
they'll even go so far as to enact martial law.
I guess they really mean business.
And here I was hoping to start on V Shipping as soon as possible.
V Shipping?
But aren't they innocent?
Didn't you tell us that they helped the army on the train?
"Vampire..."
It's nothing.
All of you get searching for Alma's management.
Yes sir!
What will you be doing, Major?
I feel like pretending to be someone other than a reporter today.
A way to live other than revenge?
Nice! New record!
So this is how we use it.
The Japanese sure don't hold back on the hot water!
Before I came here, I'd only heard about it from my mom.
What?
I never knew you had a brother.
Yep.
But I'd always thought he was dead.
Then you're lucky you ended up meeting him.
As a vampire, though.
Vampire or not, isn't that way better than never being able to meet him again?
So this is how you got the skill you showed on that train.
My father scolded me for being there.
He told me to stop practicing swordsmanship and focus on my studies.
That's such a waste!
Everyone loves a woman who can fight.
Why did you start working for V Shipping, Dorothea?
Wouldn't you much rather hear about why Yuliy did?
There you go with that again!
I came from a fairly well-off household,
though not as wealthy as yours.
I never wanted for anything.
Then why did you...
Because I saw.
I saw a monster that can't be allowed to exist.
A vampire.
I feel the same.
Anyone who saw a monster like that wouldn't want to put it out of their mind.
They couldn't just ignore it.
They'd have to do something about it!
Y-Yeah.
And that's all you needed to put your life on the line to protect the people from them.
You're amazing.
You're thinking too highly of me.
I just had a fire in my heart that I couldn't keep down.
It was just me being a reckless kid.
You've learned, seen, and heard things from all over the world, right?
I'm very jealous of that.
Then would you mind teaching me, too?
"Sword-fighting," was it?
That's something I haven't learned.
Gladly.
It's called "swordsmanship," though.
Yeah.
Then let's meet at the bar, as usual.
You're new.
There's been a lot of reorganization.
That's hardly unusual, is it?
I need information about Alma Company's missing managers.
Everyone and their mother seems to.
I already know that they were on the train that the
Hyakko Party attacked, but nothing of what they did next.
They were? That's news to me.
If you don't know, I'll go ask someone else.
I suppose that means that those managers are vampires, then?
I'm Major Iba Hideomi of the Japanese Imperial Army.
The Army?
I need you to tell me everything you know.
Right! A job well done!
They won't be able to complain if I charge them big for this.
Cold out here.
Damn it!
Why is the Army involved?
What the hell is going on?
Connect me to 7036 Yotsuya, the Naoe household—
Oh, I'm sorry, but we're not open for...
Stay with me!
It's fine.
I haven't been bitten.
Listen...
Take this.
Here...
Vampire...
They're...
Attack you...
I wish I could have had one of your Mockingbirds one last time.
The Professor sure is late.
Put him through.
How can he be out drinking at this hour?
Professor?
Right.
Understood.
You stay safe as well.
Vampires are coming.
Time to work!
Now we don't have to go looking for them!
We need to get all of the people in the mansion to safety,
and then set traps throughout the house, starting at the entrances.
Got it!
Yuliy.
There's something I need you to do.
They're coming?
Is there anywhere in the house to hide?
There's the storehouse in the annex.
But why are you telling me?
We need you to convince the Baron to take everyone in the house there.
You've actually seen and fought vampires before, so I know you'll be able to do it.
Yuliy!
That's what Dorothea told me to say.
I see.
Very well.
Um...
You want me to hide too, right?
No, I want you to protect your father and servants.
Everyone says that you're really strong.
All right!
What are you doing?
Just setting a little bug trap.
Tonight's going to be rough.
You'd do well to stay inside.
I see...
What is this, Ryouko?
Why are you dressed like that?
Monsters are coming to attack this house.
What are you talking about?
It's the truth.
We must head straight to the storeroom.
What a disaster...
How could something like this happen?
Father, so you know about the monsters—
My Ryouko's finally lost her mind...
I have not!
What is this? A blackout?
Father!
Please, we must hurry!
They're here.
Using guns would give away our position.
Come on, you filthy vampires.
Let's get this over with and take another bath.
Do you want to kill me too, Philip?
What?
One of my race killed your parents.
Why are you asking that now?
Who knows.
Thinking back, him being a Sirius had nothing to do with it.
That was just...
Just bad luck.
Do you want revenge?
Have you never had the urge to kill all of the kin of the person who killed your parents?
Sure I have.
But don't you remember what Saki said?
It wasn't your fault.
Doesn't the same thing apply to your brother?
Does the fact that you have to get revenge on the vampires
really mean that you have to get revenge on your brother?
They're falling for the traps.
It's stopped.
Easy.
Fallon.
They're not coming.
You think they ran away?
They're here.
They're close.
What? Where?
There's nowhere for them to hide here!
I can smell them.
Shit. We're pulling back!
Philip!
Yuliy!
This is bad. They're staging an all out war!
Let's find Dorothea and Fallon!
Look, it's a fire!
Whose mansion is that?
That's Baron Naoe's estate!
It looks like the stage has been set quite nicely.
Let's begin.
Just what is going on here, Ryouko?
The members of V Shipping are fighting.
What?
What is that supposed to mean?
I'll buy time if I have to.
Please take that chance to lead everyone out of here to safety.
Don't be a fool!
You'll do no such thing!
As the next head of this household, I have a responsibility to protect—
What kind of father wants to be protected by his daughter?
I will go!
Ryouko...
If anything happened to you, how could I ever face your mother in heaven?
Father...
This isn't good.
I haven't even sent any money home this month!
If you die, they'll get the insurance.
Shut the hell up.
Crap, the fire's spreading!
Kershner!
Looks like we've got a big one, Yuliy.
"Yuliy"?
So you're the last living Sirius.
I'll do you the honor of killing you myself.
Hey, don't go ignoring me!
Brother!
Philip!
You're going to fight me!
Foolish.
You should have just abandoned that useless human.
Yuliy...
Get out of here...
I will.
With you by my side!
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
We have obtained a certain ancient text.
That could affect the very existence of the Empire.
It was because you were there for me that I've lived this long.
You would have me believe such a thing really exists?
Yes, it's been a long time indeed, Kershner!